{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": " You ________ throw litter on the streets.\n",
            "a": "mustn't ",
            "b": "couldn't      ",
            "c": "needn't       ",
            "d": "won't",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "29",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " My mother permitted me to go out at night. She said,\" You ________  go out tonight\"\n",
            "a": "may ",
            "b": "have to        ",
            "c": "must ",
            "d": "ought to",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "29",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " They can type. They ________ type.\n",
            "a": "learn how to    ",
            "b": "are able to    ",
            "c": "know how to ",
            "d": "both B&C",
            "answer": "4",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "29",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " He advised me to take an English course. I ________ take it early.\n",
            "a": "should ",
            "b": "shall ",
            "c": "will ",
            "d": "may",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "29",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " I'd rather ________ in the field than ________ home.\n",
            "a": "to work/ to stay ",
            "b": "work/ stay",
            "c": "working/ staying ",
            "d": "worked / stayed",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "29",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " As an orphan, he ________ earn his living alone.\n",
            "a": "have to ",
            "b": "has had to    ",
            "c": "ought to       ",
            "d": "had to",
            "answer": "4",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "29",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " They prayed that their daughter ________ be lucky again.\n",
            "a": "may ",
            "b": "will ",
            "c": "could ",
            "d": "might",
            "answer": "4",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "29",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " He ________ all that money, so she could save some.\n",
            "a": "didn't need to spend ",
            "b": "needn't have spent",
            "c": "shouldn't spend ",
            "d": "shouldn't to spend",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "29",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " He spent all that money last week. He ________ so much.\n",
            "a": "didn't need to spend ",
            "b": "shouldn't spend",
            "c": "needn't have spent ",
            "d": "didn't have to spend",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "29",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " He had to work hard so that he ________ his family.\n",
            "a": "may support    ",
            "b": "supported     ",
            "c": "can support   ",
            "d": "might support",
            "answer": "4",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "29",
            "type": "1"
        }
    ]
}